pokerspace.com 2010-12-29

# Privacy - Legal - Pokerspace

.

Effective October 15th, 2007

  * The Information We Collect
  * Minimum Age Requirement
  * Use of Information Obtained by Pokerspace
  * Inviting Friends
  * Email Notifications
  * Market Research Surveys
  * Affiliate Offers
  * Use of Cookies
  * Third-Party Advertisers
  * Links
  * Merger or Acquisition
  * Security
  * Contact

Pokerspace is a social network that allows its members to share information within the community. We believe that all members should have full control over their information and the way it’s shared. Therefore we have implemented a reasonable set of standard default settings which a User can easily adjust his/her preferences. 

### The Information We Collect

Top

Once you open an account you agree to sharing the information you provide with Pokerspace. We cannot delete accounts from Pokerspace. If, in the unfortunate circumstance, you would like to delete your account with Pokerspace, we would be happy to delete your details and suspend the account, but a complete deletion from Pokerspace history is not possible. 

When you visit Pokerspace you provide us with two types of information: personal information that you knowingly choose to disclose and information collected as you interact with the Pokerspace platform.

When you register with Pokerspace, you provide us with certain personal information, such as your name, your email address, your telephone number, your address, your gender, schools attended and any other personal or preference information that you choose to provide to us. 

When you use Pokerspace, you may set up your personal profile, form relationships, send messages, perform searches and queries, form groups, set up events, and transmit information through various channels. We collect this information so that we can provide you the service and offer personalized features. In most cases, we retain it so that, for instance, you can return to view prior messages you have sent or easily see your friend list. When you update information, we usually keep a backup copy of the prior version for a reasonable period of time to enable reversion to the prior version of that information. 

You post User Content (as defined in the Pokerspace Terms and Conditions) on the site at your own risk. Although we allow you to set privacy options that limit access to your pages, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot control the actions of other Users with whom you may choose to share your pages and information. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that User Content you post on the site will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the site. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal, copies of User Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other Users have copied or stored your User Content. 

Pokerspace may also collect information about you from other sources, such as newspapers, blogs, instant messaging services, and other Users of the Pokerspace service through the operation of the service in order to provide you with more useful information and a more personalized experience. By using Pokerspace, you are consenting to have your personal data transferred to and processed in Canada. 

Any improper collection or misuse of information provided on Pokerspace is a violation of the Pokerspace Terms and Conditions and should be reported to privacy@Pokerspace.com

### Minimum Age Requirement

Top

No one under the age of 18 is permitted to use Pokerspace.com or any of its affiliates and subsidiaries. In some cases the affiliates may have a higher minimum age requirement. For these sites their minimum age requirement overrides that of Pokerspace.

### Use of Information Obtained by Pokerspace

Top

When you register with Pokerspace, you create your own profile and privacy settings. Your profile information, as well as your name, email and photo, are displayed to people allowed privacy settings to enable you to connect with people on Pokerspace. We may occasionally use your name and email address to send you notifications regarding new services offered by Pokerspace that we think you may find valuable. 

Profile information is used by Pokerspace primarily to be presented back to and edited by you when you access the service and to be presented to others permitted to view that information by your privacy settings. In some cases where your privacy settings permit it (e.g., posting to your chatboard), other Pokerspace Users may be able to supplement your profile. 

Your name, and profile picture thumbnail will be available in search results across the Pokerspace network. This is primarily so your friends can find you and send a buddy request. People who see your name in searches, however, will not be able to access your profile information unless they have a relationship to you (friend, friend of friend, member of your networks, etc.) that allows such access based on your privacy settings. 

Pokerspace may send you service-related announcements from time to time through the general operation of the service. For instance, if a friend sends you a new message or event invitation, or someone posts on your chatboard, you may receive an email alerting you of such requests. 

Pokerspace may use information in your profile without identifying you as an individual to third parties. We do this for purposes such as aggregating how many people in a network like a band or movie and personalizing advertisements and promotions. You can know more about the world around you they're more likely to be interesting to you. For example, if you put a favorite poker website, we might post offers about this website so you’re update and connected to things you enjoy.

We may use information about you that we collect from other sources, including but not limited to newspapers and Internet sources such as blogs, instant messaging services, Pokerspace Platform developers and other Users of Pokerspace, to supplement your profile. Where such information is used, we generally allow you to specify in your privacy settings that you do not want this to be done or to take other actions that limit the connection of this information to your profile. 

### Inviting Friends

Top

When inviting friends to join the site you may enter their email addresses directly, or use one of our import options to import friend's lists. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. We do not store any of your friend's email addresses if they decline your invitation and do not join the site. We do not store any other information you provide to import friend's lists or invite friends. Such information is provided only and directly to the program or website you have selected to import your contacts from. 

As with any site that uses invitations and buddy lists, you should use care when disclosing your personal information to strangers. Be advised that if you send messages containing personal information, that information may be collected and used by others.

### Email Notifications

Top

The following kinds of optional notifications may be sent to you by email, depending on your chosen preferences. The notifications can be configured by going to the “Preferences” page on Pokerspace. This functionality may not be available during the first release, but is a part of the Pokerspace product roadmap.

  * Buddy Notification: When someone adds you as a buddy
  * Message Notification: When someone writes you a new message
  * Poker Crew Notification: When someone invites to their crew
  * Event: When someone invites you to an event
  * Group: When someone invites you to a group
  * Blog: When someone comments on your blog 
  * Photo: When someone comments on a photo of yours

### Market Research Surveys

Top

If you choose to earn extra PS Points by completing surveys offered by our research partners, the information you submit in completing this survey will be transmitted to them. However none of this information will be personally identifiable – it shall be used for research purposes only, and in aggregate form. You will know what the survey is about before you take it, and will have the option of canceling it at anytime before or during the survey. We do not work or associate with research companies that are in the business of trading personal information. 

### Affiliate Offers

Top

You can sign up for a promotional offer by an advertiser to earn PS Points. This will require you to click on a link, and leave the Pokerspace site. Affiliate Offers typically require your name, age, location, and email address, though they may require more information. THIS INFORMATION IS TRANSMITTED TO THE ADVERTISER. ANY INFORMATION YOU ENTER ON ANY SITE AFTER LEAVING POKERSPACE.COM BECOMES THE PROPERTY OF THE ADVERTISER, AND ITS USE IS GOVERNED BY THE ADVERTISERS’ PRIVACY POLICY. Before entering any information into an affiliate offer, you are advised to be aware of the advertisers’ privacy policies and their use of your information.

### Use of Cookies

Top

When you enter Pokerspace, we collect your browser type and IP address. This information is gathered for all Pokerspace visitors. In addition, we store certain information from your browser using "cookies." A cookie is a piece of data stored on the User's computer tied to information about the User. We use session ID cookies to confirm that Users are logged in. These cookies terminate once the User closes the browser. By default, we use a persistent cookie that stores your login ID (but not your password) to make it easier for you to login when you come back to Pokerspace. You can remove or block this cookie using the settings in your browser if you want to disable this convenience feature. 

### Third-Party Advertisers

Top

The ads appearing on Pokerspace are delivered to Users by our Web advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may set cookies. Doing this allows the ad network to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad networks may compile information about your location, or others who are using your computer that saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. We do not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third-party ad servers or ad networks. 

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Pokerspace, and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Links

Top

Pokerspace may contain links to other websites. We are of course not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage our Users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by Pokerspace.

### Merger or Acquisition

Top

We reserve the right to transfer your personal information in the event of a transfer of ownership of Pokerspace.com, such as acquisition by or merger with another company. If an acquiring company should plan to materially change this privacy policy, we will notify you beforehand.

### Security

Top

The security of your personal information depends on your protection of your account password. Please do not disclose your account password to unauthorized people. Pokerspace uses industry standard technology designed to help keep your personal information safe. If you have any other questions about the security of our website, please contact us. Please note that you may not opt-out of receiving important service or security updates.

Changes in Privacy Policy

From time to time we may update this Privacy Policy and will post a notice of any significant changes on our website. You should visit this page periodically to review any such changes to the privacy policy. Your continued use of this website or our service and/or continued provision of personally identifiable information to us will be subject to the terms of the then-current Privacy Policy.

### Contact

Top

For any questions or concerns related to this privacy statement or Pokerspace, please contact:
